Guide to the Cornell Information Technologies records,1940-2009.
Cornell Information Technologies Records
- 370 Planning (Box 30)
  - Original Documents, 1973
  - Loads, 1972
  - Inputs, 1972-1973
- Report - Recommendation to Increase Computing Capacity at OCS, 1973-07 (Box 30)
  Prepared by the UCB
- IBM Proposal to Cornell on 370/168 and supporting materials, 1973-06 (Box 30)
- SU - College of Forestry, 1974-1976 (Box 31)
- FPS Array Processor, 1977 (Box 31)
- FPS - Fortran Negotations, 1977 (Box 31)
- Management Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 31)
- SALawrence Staff Meetings, 1977-80 (Box 31)
- Organizations - Stanford University, 1975 (Box 31)
- Organizations _ Other Universities, 1966 (Box 31)
- NCAR Computing, 1973-1977 (Box 31)
- Hiltz/Manning/Aikin - On Campus Needs (3 folders), 1972 (Box 31)
- PL/C Project ( 2 folders), 1968-76 (Box 31)
- Dave Pulleyn Special odds/end File, 1969-73 (Box 31)
  The rift in 1969-70 and Erik McWilliams departure
- Regional Reports, Studies, etc, 1972-1976 (Box 31)
- TC3 Regional, 1974-1975 (Box 31)
- OCS Staff Issues, Manual, incidentals, 1968-1969 (Box 31)
- TSO, 1973-1975 (Box 31)
- 1401 Simulator, 1969-1971 (Box 31)
- Telecommunications Study, 1975 (Box 31)
- Online Space, 1974-1976 (Box 31)
- WATFIV, 1970-1973 (Box 31)
- VM (Virtual Machine), 1974-1976 (Box 31)
- Tape/Disk Utilizations, 1973-1976 (Box 31)
- Unitech (Terminal Study) (2 folders), 1973-1976 (Box 31)
- United Way Computer Account, 1978 (Box 31)
- VM Rates Accounting, 1976 (Box 31)
- Xerox Forms Printer, 1972-1973 (Box 31)
- FermiLab (Ad Hoc Committee) Future Computing Needs, 1983-1984 (Box 31)
- GLOB II Revisited, 1983 (Box 32)
- DCAA Audit, 1982 (Box 32)
- Instructional Computing: Fixed Cost, 1984 (Box 32)
- Instructional Computing: Analyses, 1985-1986 (Box 32)
- Count of Student Accounts, 1983 (Box 32)
- Administrative Allocations, 1981-1982 (Box 32)
- JSO Financial Restructure, 1981 (Box 32)
- Financial Restructuring, 1980-1981 (Box 32)
- Instructional/Research Allocations, 1981-1982 (Box 32)
- CCS Organization Charts, 1983 (Box 32)
- Cost: Langmuir Ops, Staff, Mail, 1984-1987 (Box 32)
- Allocations, 1981-1982 (Box 32)
- EDP Audit, 1988 (Box 32)
- PC Sales Review, 1985-1986 (Box 32)
- OEC - Office Equipment Center, 1986-1987 (Box 32)
- CCS and KK Stuff for the 1980s (Box 32)
  - UCB Starting with Ken King, 1980
  - Campus Terminals Project, 1981
  - Langmuir Site, 1980
  - Trustees, 1981, 1983
  - Trustee Presentation, 1981
  - 3081 Conversion, 1983
  - Trustees Backup Data, 1983
  - CCS/Trustees, 1984-1985
  - Capital Budget, 1981-1982
  - Capital Items, 1982-1983
  - Capital Items, 1983-1984
  - Capital Budget, 1983-1984
  - Capital Budget, 1984-1985
  - CCS Unit Plan for the 80s, 1981
  - CCS/Trustees, 1984-1985
  - Student Employment Policies, 1983
- Mass Storage (Box 33)
  - Security in the IEEE Mass Storage Ref Model, 1993
    Andrew Hanushevsky at the 12th Annual Symposium
  - Institutional File System Project Overview, 1988
  - Reference Models, 1987-1989
  - Mass Storage- Nov.89 meeting in Ithaca, 1989
  - Mass Storage - miscellaneous materials, 1989
  - Mass Storage, 1989-1990
  - Mass Storage, 1990-1991
  - University of Michigan visit, 1989
  - Conference, 1990
  - CU/IBM Supercomputing Joint Study, 1990-1992
  - Mesa Corporation (2 folders), 1988
- Mesa Corporation (2 folders), 1989 (Box 33)
- Data Tree, 1989 (Box 33)
- Mass Storage - Institutional File System Project Overview, 1988 (Box 33)
- Project Report: Distributed Storage System Access Control (Hanushevsky and Len Silver), 1993 (Box 33)
- Cornell Theory Center Program Plan to NSF, AIX and Unix issues, 1990 (Box 33)
- 3081 w/VM; Floating Point Arithmetic Problem, 1984 (Box 33)
- NOTIS-CIT Cost Estimate, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
- VM Scheduler Documentation, 1982 (Box 33)
- Cornell Tape Driven Scheduler for VM/SP (Bob Cowles), 1982 (Box 33)
- 3380 DASD Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
- MDM/VM Scheduler Requests, 1980 (Box 33)
- One Stop Shop, 1989 (Box 33)
- CIT NetID Distribution, 1993 (Box 33)
- PSF Confidentiality Statements ( 2 folders), 1985-1986 (Box 33)
- Master's Project Report (Thomas K. Bauer, Enrique Del Castillo, Thierry P. Girard), 1988 (Box 33)
  An Analysis of Inventory Policies and Warehouse Space Allocation of General Stores, Cornell University
- Terminal Enterprise, 1979-1981 (Box 34)
- DEC20 Operations, 1979-1981 (Box 34)
- DEC20 Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 34)
- DEC Academic Materials/Vaxen, etc (include Cornell Vax Manager), 1985 (Box 34)
- Tymshare Agreements, 1979-1981 (Box 34)
- Tymnet Specs by Tymshare, Inc, 1979 (Box 34)
- B and PA/DEC system contract, 1980-1983 (Box 34)
- Knoll Pharmaceutical, 1980-1982 (Box 34)
- Clarkson College Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 34)
- Clarkson College Visit, 1974 (Box 34)
- Telco Study, 1979 (Box 34)
- Dryden School District Computer Needs, 1980-1981 (Box 34)
- Terak, 1980 (Box 34)
- Computer Literacy Task Force, 1980 (Box 34)
- Network Plans and Budgets, 1981 (Box 34)
- Academic Custom Programming Rates, 1981 (Box 34)
- CCS starting with Stuart Lynn, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
- Library-NOTIS Team, 1986-1988 (Box 34)
- BITNET, 1987-1989 (Box 34)
- PINCNET, ethernet, etc, 1987 (Box 34)
- Payroll Forms, 1980-1989 (Box 34)
- CU Comparable Institutional Data Survey, 1974 (Box 34)
- CU Comparable Institutional Data Survey, 1975 (Box 34)
- IPA Comparative Data, 1975-1979 (Box 34)
- Planning for Higher Education, 1975-1978 (Box 34)
- Long-range Planning for Higher Education (D. Sherman), 1971 (Box 34)
- IPA Indicators, 1977-1979 (Box 34)
- Payroll/Personnel Forms, Paperwork, etc, 1981-1983 (Box 34)
- Computing Plan for the 80s, 1979-1980 (Box 34)
- J Rudan/Applicants for Director of Computing, 1979-1980 (Box 34)
- Systems Files (include TSO), 1978-1979 (Box 34)
  CM Support-Bob Hyman, 16 bit micro, TSO Acc'ting, Fast Dump/restore Implementing IT in 1973
- Funding Opportunities: Mass Storage Sys, 1978 (Box 34)
- Hardware: Terak Instructional Computing, 1979 (Box 34)
  The Great Terak Project as called by Conway
- Hardware: Microcomputer Design - Grimes Jungle Terak Proposal, 1978 (Box 34)
- Teraks for data entry in Financial Aid/Admissions, 1980 (Box 34)
- NetComm Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 35)
- OCS Operations/Budgets, 1988-1989 (Box 35)
- CCS Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 35)
- Library System Issues, 1989 (Box 35)
- Instructional Computing, 1990 (Box 35)
- CR/IR Management, 1989 (Box 35)
- Services Committee, 1989 (Box 35)
- CISER Agreement and Planning, 1989-1993 (Box 35)
  includes selected copies of SyntheCISER newsletter
- CIT/CNSF Plans (JWR), 1990 (Box 35)
- ADABAS - HPE/Complete, 1992 (Box 35)
- Sr Management - monthly, 1989 (Box 35)
- Sr Management - monthly, 1990 (Box 35)
- Sr Management one file, 1991 (Box 35)
- Capacity Planning, 1990 (Box 35)
- CNSF Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 35)
- Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 35)
- Budget Review with MSL, 1990-1991 (Box 35)
- Coupling Project/Contract, 1988-1989 (Box 35)
- Applicants for Asst Director of REA, 1989 (Box 35)
- Applicants for Systems Programmer, 1989 (Box 35)
- Abstracts - Research on the CNSF, 1989 (Box 35)
- Abstracts - Research on the CNSF, 1990 (Box 35)
- Science and Supercomputing on the CNSF, 1989 (Box 35)
- Supercomputing/CNSF/Theory Center (Box 36)
  - Theory Center Building Plans, 1987
  - Theory Center Space, 1987
  - CNSF Facilities Management, 1988
  - CNSF 2nd 600E Planning, 1988
  - AIX/ESP, 1988
  - UNIX, 1988
  - Theory Center Building and Computer Room, 1988
  - Theory Center Space, 1989
  - CCC - Theory Center, 1989
  - Split Operations: CNSF/CIT, 1988-1989
  - CNSF: Coupling, 1990
  - AIX/370, 1989-1990
  - CNSF: Big Move Cost Estimates, 1990
  - CNSF Misc, 1990-1991
  - CNSF Move Team Project, 1992
  - Cornell Theory Center Program Plan, 1992
  - IBM Highly Parallel Supercomputing System Laboratory Proposal, 1992
  - CIT-Theory Center Split, 1991-92
  - CNSF Planning Meetings, 1991
  - CIT-Theory Center Split (2 folders), 1991-1992
  - Separation of CIT-Theory Center (2 folders), 1991-1992
  - CNSF, 1991
  - CNSF "Buzz 1 - Coupling Joint Study, etc, 1990
  - CNSF "Buzz 2 - Hotovy Comes, Int'l Outreach, 2 machine rooms, 1990
  - CNSF "Buzz 3 - RS-6000s, AIX, etc, 1990
  - CNSF "Buzz 4 - AIX, machine moves, etc, 1990
- CCC Initial Planning (Program Statement), 1984 (Box 37)
- CCC Project and Plans, 1983-1987 (Box 37)
- Langmuir Move, 1986-1987 (Box 37)
- Alterations to Comstock Hall - Project Manual by HOLT, 1985 (Box 37)
- CCS Contracts, 1986 (Box 37)
- CCS Policies and Procedures, 1986 (Box 37)
- Cornell Theory Center Quarterly (Box 37)
  - Report to the National Science Foundation, 1986-01-1986-03
  - Report to the National Science Foundation, 1986-04-1986-06
  - Report to the National Science Foundation, 1986-07-1986-09
  - Report to the National Science Foundation, 1986-10-1986-12
- CNSF Site Visit, 1987 (Box 37)
- CNSF Publications (Box 37)
- CNSF Misc, 1987-88 (Box 37)
- Theory Center - Meta Center Design Study, 1993 (Box 37)
- Production Supercomputing Facility (Box 37)
  - PSF Hardware, 1985
  - PSF Staff, Space, etc, 1985
  - Theory Center Publications, 1985
  - PSF Telecomm, 1985
  - PSF Software, 1985
  - PSF Costs and Sharing, 1986
  - PSF Accounting Services, 1985
  - PSF, IBM, NSF, etc, 1984-1985
  - PSF Configuration and Staging, 1985
  - PSF Misc, 1985
  - Computer Rates, 1979-1983
  - Computer Billing and Income Reports, 1980-1983
  - CCS Complaints and Feedback, 1981-1986
  - Systems Installation, 1988-1989
- MSA Management Systems and Analysis (Box 38)
  - Housing Lottery System Documentation, 1974
  - Non-Academic Retirement Plan, 1966
  - Cornell Store Inventory System, 1971
  - Cornell Facilities Inventory System Guide, 1972
  - EAS Tuition Program - design specs, 1974
  - Cornell Loan Programs, 1971
  - Report of the FAO/SAO Process Study Committee, 1970
  - Advanced Placement Subsystem, 1971
    Procedure and Operations Manual
  - Missing Records Program - design specs 1974, 1974
  - Statistic File Extract Program - design specs, 1973
  - Term Average Card Program - design spec, 1974
  - SIS Test Plan, 1973
  - ACT/SISELECT Subsystem - design specs, 1974
  - Student Information Systems - SIS, 1967-1968
  - Payroll/Personnel System Costs, 1973
  - VPI Student Record System, 1972
  - MSA Central File System, 1975
  - User's Requirements Documentation Guide, 1974
  - Hazeltine 2000 Terminal Guide, 1974
  - Database Administration at Cornell, 1973
  - Summary of Admin Data Processing, 1975
  - Admin Support System description, 1973
  - Motor Vehicle Data Base - design specs, 1973
  - Interim Summer Session Registration System report, 1972
  - Software Documentation for the Ballot Counting system, 1975
  - CU Project Admin Support System - design spec, 1971
  - Public Affairs Profile File - design specs, 1973
  - Revised Public Affairs Profile File, 1977
  - OCS Correspondence, 1978
  - Policies and Procedures, 1979
  - Payroll System, 1979
  - SBO Contract and Associated Costs, 1979
  - Agreement between SBO and OCS, 1979
  - IBM Instructional Computing Joint Study, 1979
  - Task Force on Computer Policy, 1979
- Student Billing and Charge Card System - design specs, 1971 (Box 39)
- University Non-retail consolidated student Billing and Accts Receivable, 1971 (Box 39)
- SIS - the Active Subsystem of SIS -preliminary systems description, 1972 (Box 39)
- SIS - proposed Active Subsystem for CU - study/report, 1972 (Box 39)
- SIS Active Subsystem - development and implementation, 1972 (Box 39)
- SIS Test Plan, 1973 (Box 39)
- Graduate Financial Support - student employees and assistantships, 1972 (Box 39)
- Financial Aid Accounting Office - draft/review, 1972 (Box 39)
- Procedures in awarding Student Financial Aid, 1972 (Box 39)
- Proposed Student Financial Aid System - overview, 1973 (Box 39)
- Student Financial System for CU, 1974 (Box 39)
- Requested Proposal for a Pennsylvania based Student Record System, 1975 (Box 39)
- Univ of Penn SIS vs Cornell requirements, 1975 (Box 39)
- Motor Vehicle data processing, 1974 (Box 39)
- Cornell Active SIS: report and proposal, 1974 (Box 39)
- Administrative computing at Cornell, 1979 (Box 39)
- Course Schedule Maintenance Module, 1985 (Box 39)
- Project Administration Support System Description, 1973 (Box 39)
- Final Exam Scheduler - User's Guide, 1976 (Box 39)
- Public Affairs Profile File - design specs, 1974 (Box 39)
- MSA Programming Standards, 1974 (Box 39)
- Payroll/Personnel System - database description, 1972 (Box 39)
- Housing Deposit Address Create Program - design specs, 1973 (Box 39)
- Term Average Card Program - design specs, 1974 (Box 39)
- Ballot Counting Program - software documentation, 1975 (Box 39)
- System Description Documentation - outline and requirements, 1973 (Box 39)
- MSA Guide to User's Requirements - documentation, 1974 (Box 39)
- Revised Preprinted Voucher Project - detailed program specs, 1975 (Box 39)
- Improving Information Systems at Cornell University, 1970 (Box 39)
  Study by H. G. Vaughan
- Payroll System Package Review, 1970 (Box 39)
- Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 40)
- Budget Review, 1980-05 (Box 40)
- Plans, 1980-1981 (Box 40)
- Income/Expense Review, 1980-09 (Box 40)
- Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 40)
- Expense Summary, 1980-1981 (Box 40)
- Year End Options, 1980-1981 (Box 40)
- Budget Review, 1981-02 (Box 40)
- Budget Analyses, 1981-1982 (Box 40)
- 610K/700K Fund, 1981 (Box 40)
- Income, 1981-1982 (Box 40)
- Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 40)
- Capital Projects/Status Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 40)
- Budget: year end, 1982 (Box 40)
- Budget: Final Summary 1982-1983 (Box 40)
- Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 40)
- Budget; Year End, 1982-1983 (Box 40)
- CCS Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 40)
- Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 40)
- Administrative Data Processing - Operations Manual for Day Hall (Stephan Knapp and Peter Baker), 1980 (Box 40)
- Adabas - Recommendation to Install for Admin Systems, 1980-10 (Box 40)
  Report by Tom Dimock, chair, Software Evaluation Committee
- Cornell Program Synthesizer Tutorial (for the Terak) (Tim Teitelbaum), 1980 (Box 40)
- Financial and Planning Services 1979-80 Budget and Plans, 1979-04 (Box 40)
  OCS, Controllers Office, Institutional Planning and Analysis
- OCS Usage Analysis Year ending June 1977, 1977-06 (Box 40)
- OCS Computing Expense by Department June1980, 1980-06 (Box 40)
- College Computing Reports and Responses, 1986-1987 (Box 40)
  Hum Ec, CALS - Galloway response, ILR
- College Computing Reports _ CALS on Word Processing, 1981 (Box 40)
  2 folders of input information from units
- College Computing Reports - Toward an Integrated, 1986 (Box 40)
  Information Systems for CALS
- IBM/CCS Joint Study TCP/IP, 1986-1987 (Box 40)
- MVS Conversion Tasks, status,etc, Conversion Guide, Announement, 1983 (Box 40)
- CUDA - Cornell University Distributed Accounting System, 1986-1988 (Box 40)
  Various Presentations on why, what, etc
- Academic Computing Newsletter, Vol 1, #1, 1983 (Box 40)
  Spring
- Student Handouts on Computing, 1987 (Box 40)
- VM/IX Final Report -Richard Alexander et al, 1984 (Box 40)
- Ricemail -Issues Surrounding the Installation of Ricemail, 1987-1988 (Box 40)
- Intellectual Property Rights Issues - Mass Store, VM/XA, 1988 (Box 40)
- Bonus Payment Policy Langmuir to CCC Computer Move, 1986-12 (Box 40)
- CCS Retreat Feb 1988 - Planning Papers, etc, 1988 (Box 40)
- F and BO, 1989-1994 (Box 41)
- Hewlett-Packard 755 Grant, 1993 (Box 41)
- M and BO (Management and Budget Office), 1989-1990 (Box 41)
- Cornell in 10 Years, the Influence of Technology, 1992 (Box 41)
  Report of the 2001 Committee
- Layoffs, 1992 (Box 41)
- IBM Joint Study (Software Exclusions), 1986 (Box 41)
- CIT Reorganization, 1993-1994 (Box 41)
- Classification Review Study, 1993 (Box 41)
- Budget Initiatives, 1994 (Box 41)
- CR Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 41)
- Information Systems for the 21st Century, 1992 (Box 41)
- Qualtec: Quality Improvement Process (2 folders), 1992 (Box 41)
- Public Sector Financials, 1995-05 (Box 41)
- HR/Payroll System, 1995 (Box 41)
- HR/Payroll System, 1994-1996 (Box 41)
- Manuals, Tech Specs, 1994-1995 (Box 41)
- PeopleSoft and Cornell Contract, 1995-12 (Box 41)
- PeopleSoft Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box 41)
- PeopleSoft System Scope Docs (financial, grant mgmt, student), 1995 (Box 41)
- PeopleSoft Planning Documents - All Systems -Part 1, 1995-1996 (Box 41)
- PeopleSoft Planning Documents - All Systems/IBM -Part 2, 1995-1996 (Box 41)
- PeopleSoft Planning Documents - All Systems -Part 3, 1995-1996 (Box 41)
- PeopleSoft Planning Documents - All Systems -Part 4, 1995-1996 (Box 41)
- PeopleSoft - CU Kickoff for HR and Payroll Implementation, 1996-01 (Box 41)
- Server Status (report on # and type of servers in CIT), 1992-12 (Box 42)
- CSARS - CR Income Reports (monthly designated funds), 1989-1994 (Box 42)
- Data Entry - replace CADE system with Unisys Data Entry Sys, 1991 (Box 42)
- Design Options for Developing WWW Applications - CIT Pub, 1995-10 (Box 42)
- Reorganizing CR (Team based organization), 1993-1994 (Box 42)
- CIT Budget Reviews, Preparation and Reports, 1990-1994 (Box 42)
- IR Quarterly Reviews - Handouts, agenda, etc, 1994 (Box 42)
- CIT Directory - Services and Staff, 1996-01 (Box 42)
- Magnetic Tapes - Library and other issues, 1990 (Box 42)
- A Users Guide to Electronic Mail CIT Publication, 1990 (Box 42)
  Adapted from Rice University, Doc # COMM 6
- Library/CIT Joint Planning Sessions systems/computers, 1992 (Box 42)
- IR/DT Transformation (Splitting IR into two parts), 1994 (Box 42)
- SPIRIT - CIT service providers survey report, 1994-02 (Box 42)
- Results/Recommendations Focus Group Internal Communications, 1995 (Box 42)
- MVS/ESA issues, etc, 1990-1991 (Box 42)
- CornellC Mainframe Upgrade - Supporting Materials, 1990 (Box 42)
- CornellC Mainframe Upgrade - Final Report, 1990 (Box 42)
- CornellC Capacity Planning (and peripherals), 1992 (Box 42)
- PEP - Performance Enhancement Project - CornellC upgrade, 1992 (Box 42)
- CornellC Capacity Planning and Peripheral Configuration, 1995-1996 (Box 42)
- S/390 5 year Recommendation for Continuing Need CornellC, 2000 (Box 42)
  Jim Doolittle Report for keeping mainframe capacity after P2K fails
- QIP Materials - Basic Principles, Organization, Teams, etc, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
- EZ-Backup Materials - Technical, Publicity, Rates, 2000-11 (Box 42)
- CU University Wide Strategic Planning - Institutional Planning and Research (Box 42)
  - Consultation Draft Plan - Task Force Reports, 1994-05
  - Environmental Assessment - Study Group Reports, 1993-05
  - Stakeholder Analysis - Survey Project Final Report, 1993-05
- Y2K Materials from John McKeown, project director, 1999-12 (Box 42)
  Publicity, reports, memos, responsibilities, summary
- Y2K Notes, etc from Eric Banford, 1999 (Box 42)
- The New World of Work - Business Week, 1994-10 (Box 42)
- Project 2000! - Organizing for Implementation of new Core Systems, 1995-11 (Box 42)
  Foils on Organization, Schedule, Costs
- Understanding Technologies and Architectures of Distributed, 1994-05 (Box 42)
  Environments by Robert D. Cowles at CU Report
- Joint Study in Digital Preservation - Phase 1 Report (Kenney and Personius), 1990-1991 (Box 42)
- CornellC Capacity Planning and Performance, 1990-01 (Box 42)
- Help Desk use by Colleges 1990-1993, 1993 (Box 42)
- Ithaca Gun Site for Computing Center, 1990 (Box 42)
- Computer Hacker Lands on his Feet - Syracuse Herald American, 2000-12 (Box 42)
  An Update on Robert T. Morris of the Computer Worm 12 years later.
- SUPER! Super1 Organizing Materials/Steering Committee Minutes, etc, 1988 (Box 42)
- SUPER! Conference, 1988-04 (Box 42)
- Super! Conference - Inaugural Meeting in Ithaca, 1988-04 (Box 42)
- SUPER! - Materials for the Session on Performance Issues chaired by Rudan, 1988 (Box 42)
- SUPER! - University of Kentucky, 1989 (Box 42)
- SUPER! - 4th Annual Meeting in Park City, Utah, 1991-04 (Box 42)
- SUPER! - 5th Annual Meeting at Penn State program, etc, 1992 (Box 42)
- Building Supercomputing Unix/AIX by John Rudan, 1991 (Box 42)
  Slides from presentation at SUPEUR in Rome, Italy
- EZ-Print Services/Laser Printing/EZ-Publish usage, 1991-1993 (Box 42)
- Sponsored Project System - System Concept, 1995-07 (Box 42)
  Report prepared by American Management Systems, Inc
- CCD Meeting Notes, 1993 (Box 42)
- Grad School Web Application Project Proposal (Steve. Lutter), 1995-12 (Box 42)
- Terminals in Dorms - A feasibility study, 1974 (Box 42)
  IE9311 Student Report (Giaimo and McBurnett)
- Dormitory Pilot Project, 1986 (Box 42)
- RESNET - Pilot Project - Phase 1 report Model Design Statement and other related materials on the project in 1991, 1991-05 (Box 42)
- ResNet PAR - Project Approval Request and other materials, 1995 (Box 42)
- Old Manuals from the 1950s, '60s, '70s
- Control Data 1604/160A Manuals from Tom Dimock (Box 43)
  - Fortran63 Reference Manual
  - Library Routines
  - Coop Monitor Operator's Guide
  - Edap - Cornell Educational Assembly Program by Richard Greenberg, 1964
    Programmers Manual (A companion to CORC) An in core assembly program
  - Codap1 Reference Manual
  - Oak Ridge Algol Compiler
  - COBOL Reference Manual
  - 8090 Computer System Manual
- Other Manuals contributed by Tom Dimock (Box 43)
  - CORC - the Cornell Computing Language 2nd printing, 1962-09
  - IBM 650 Data Processing System Manual of Operations
  - Program Test Procedures for the 650 Computer for course IE 3281
  - ALPAC - A Comprehensive Linear Programming System from the Service Bureau Corporation for the IBM 7094 system, 1964-06
  - Notes on the Electronic Calculator 604, 1953
- Manuals Contributed by R. C. Lesser (Box 43)
  - An Introduction to Coding the Burroughs 220 Bulletin 509, 1958-12
  - CAP Manual - The Cornell Assembly Program for the Burroughs 220 Ist Edition (David J. Waks), 1960-07
  - An Instruction Manual for CORC - The Cornell Computing Language, 1963-09
    R. W. Conway, W. L. Maxwell and R. J. Walker, 2nd Edition
    Insert on CORC by Conway and Maxwell from Comm ACM June 1963
  - Burroughs Algebraic Compiler Refernce Manual Bull. 220-21011-P, 1961-01
    A representation of ALGOL for use with the Burroughs 220
  - 650 Programming Symbolic Optimum Assembly Programming S.O.A.P. Bulletin 1 Form 22-62 85 - 1 Copyright 1956 by IBM
  - IBM Technical Newsletter No. 11 Copyright 1956 by IBM
    A Floating Decimal Interpretive system for the IBM 650 Magnetic Drum Calculator
  - Card Programmed Electronic Calculator Model A1 Principles of Operation 3rd Revision, 1954-10
  - An Introduction to IBM Punched Card Data Processing - Student Text
  - Reference Manual - IBM Functional Wiring Principles, 1960-04
  - Reference Manual - IBM Operators' Guide (card machines), 1959-07
  - Reference Manual - IBM 59 Card Verifier (from Tom Dimock), 1965-06
  - Cornell Comp Center Unit Record Room - Manual of Operations
  - Sample punched cards for the 1401 and later for HASP
  - Fortran System for the Control Data 1604 Computer Pub 087A, 1961
  - Characteristics of the Model 1604 Computer CDC Pub 018c, 1961
  - Characteristics of the 1607 Magnetic Tape System CDC Pub 041a, 1961
  - Burroughs Algebraic Compiler Reference Manual Bull. 220-21011-P, 1961-01
  - IBM System/360 Model 20 Machine Setup Form (Card Systems) and Reference Data (programming guide)
- Manuals Contributed by John W. Rudan (Box 43)
  - CORC - the Cornell Computing Language 2nd printing, Serial 2 mimeo, 1962-09
  - CORC - An Instruction Manual for the Cornell Computing Language (Conway, Maxwell and Walker), 1963-09
  - Control Data 1604 Computer - Programming Training Manual #167 Rev, 1961-11
  - IE 3281 Course Notes, Handouts and Assignments, 1958-1959
  - IE 3281 Handouts used before Summer 1962 and Exam Papers (2 folders), 1962
  - Report on the Inservice Course in Computer Mathematics for High School Mathematics Teachers - sponsor State Education Course given by R. C Lesser and J. W. Rudan from the Cornell Comp Center, 1964